Guide to the Acquisitions Department registers, etc
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Permanent Order List: Encode I
  - 342662 - 346512 (Box 43)
  - 346513 - 350669 (Box 44)
  - 350670 - 354371 (Box 45)
  - 354372 - 358406 (Box 46)
  - 358407 - 362019 (Box 47)
  - 362021 - 365501 (Box 48)
  - 365502 - 370074 (Box 49)
  - 370075 - 372537 (Box 50)
  - 372538 - 375050 (Box 51)
  - 375051 - 380200 (Box 52)
  - 380201 - 385164 (Box 53)
  - 385165 - 389739 (Box 54)
  - 389740 - 393750 (Box 55)
  - 393751 - 398907 (Box 56)
  - 500000 - 505201 (Box 57)
  - 505202 - 508094 (Box 58)
  - 508095 - 510975 (Box 59)
  - 510976 - 513850 (Box 60)
  - 513851 - 517250 (Box 61)
  - 517251 - 519875 (Box 62)
  - 519876 - 523300 (Box 63)
  - 523301 - 526512 (Box 64)
  - 526513 - 529772 (Box 65)
  - 529773 - 533140 (Box 66)
  - 533141 - 536362 (Box 67)
  - 536363 - 539423 (Box 68)
  - 539424 - 542787 (Box 69)
  - 542788 - 546085 (Box 70)
  - 546086 - 549662 (Box 71)
  - 549663 - 554076 (Box 72)
  - 554077 - 555972 (Box 73)
  - 555973 - 558323 (Box 74)
  - 558324 - 560600 (Box 75)
  - 560601 - 563827 (Box 76)
  - 563828 - 567080 (Box 77)
  - 567081 - 571076 (Box 78)
  - 571077 - 575094 (Box 79)
  - 575095 - 578728 (Box 80)
  - 578729 - 582674 (Box 81)
  - 582675 - 586529 (Box 82)
  - 586530 - 589693 (Box 83)
  - 589694 - 593518 (Box 84)
  - 593519 - 597332 (Box 85)
  - 597333 - 600617 (Box 86)
  - 600618 - 603916 (Box 87)
  - 603917 - 607230 (Box 88)
  - 607231 - 609946 (Box 89)
  - 609947 - 613982 (Box 90)
  - 613983 - 617639 (Box 91)
  - 617640 - 621294 (Box 92)
  - 621295 - 624912 (Box 93)
  - 624913 - 628450 (Box 94)
  - 628451 - 632142 (Box 95)
  - 632143 - 635454 (Box 96)
  - 635455 - 639080 (Box 97)
  - 639081 - 642616 (Box 98)
  - 642617 - 645629 (Box 99)
  - 645630 - 648845 (Box 100)
  - 648846 - 652417 (Box 101)
  - 652418 - 656205 (Box 102)
  - 656206 - 659795 (Box 103)
  - 659796 - 664559 (Box 104)
  - 664560 - 668492 (Box 105)
  - 668493 - 672276 (Box 106)
  - 672277 - 676207 (Box 107)
  - 676208 - 680003 (Box 108)
  - 680004 - 684007 (Box 109)
  - 684008 - 688828 (Box 110)
  - 688829 - 692841 (Box 111)
  - 692842 - 696905 (Box 112)
  - 696906 - 699802 (Box 113)
  - 699803 - 702864 (Box 114)
  - 702865 - 706484 (Box 115)
  - 706485 - 710326 (Box 116)
  - 710327 - 713832 (Box 117)
  - 713833 - 718190 (Box 118)
  - 718191 - 722924 (Box 119)
  - 722925 - 727331 (Box 120)
  - 727332 - 731733 (Box 121)
  - 731734 - 736207 (Box 122)
  - 736208 - 740310 (Box 123)
  - 740311 - 744486 (Box 124)
  - 744487 - 748172 (Box 125)
  - 748173 - 751985 (Box 126)
  - 751986 - 756440 (Box 127)
  - 756441 - 760232 (Box 128)
  - 760233 - 764520 (Box 129)
  - 764521 - 768613 (Box 130)
  - 768614 - 772364 (Box 131)
  - 772365 - 776537 (Box 132)
  - 776538 - 780423 (Box 133)
  - 780424 - 784499 (Box 134)
  - 784500 - 788709 (Box 135)
  - 788710 - 793584 (Box 136)
  - 793585 - 797412 (Box 137)
  - 797413 - 802215 (Box 138)
  - 802216 - 805700 (Box 139)
  - 805701 - 810483 (Box 140)
  - 810484 - 815723 (Box 141)
  - 815724 - 819559 (Box 142)
  - 819560 - 824368 (Box 143)
  - 824369 - 827113 (Box 144)
  - 827114 - 830694 (Box 145)
  - 830695 - 833901 (Box 146)
  - 833902 - 837443 (Box 147)
  - 837444 - 841005 (Box 148)
  - 841006 - 844341 (Box 149)
  - 844342 - 848950 (Box 150)
  - 848951 - 854062 (Box 151)
  - 854063 – 859812 (Box 152)
- Series VI: Lending Service
  - 1-1500 (Box 1)
  - 42001E - 43500E (Box 2)
  - 43501E - 45160E (Box 3)
  - 46429E - 48000E (Box 4)
  - 48001E - 49400E (Box 5)
- Series VII: Order Book: Slavic Acquisitions I
  - 50001H - 52000H: October 4, 1962 - January 2, 1963 (Box 1)
  - 52001H - 54000H: January 2, 1963 - March 26, 1963 (Box 2)
  - 54001H - 56000H: March 26, 1963 - June 21, 1963 (Box 3)
  - 56001H - 58000H: June 21, 1963 - October 7, 1963 (Box 4)
  - 50501M - 52000M: October 7, 1963 - December 2, 1963 (Box 5)
  - 52001M - 54000M: December 2, 1963 - April 10, 1964 (Box 6)
  - 54001M - 56000M: April 10, 1964 - September 21, 1964 (Box 7)
  - 56001M - 58000M: September 21, 1964 - December 23, 1964 (Box 8)
  - 42001P - 44000P: December 1, 1965 - January 19, 1966 (Box 9)
  - January 28, 1966 - February 10, 1966 (Box 9)
  - 44501P - 45000P: January 19, 1966 - January 28, 1966 (Box 10)
  - 45001P - 47000P: October 8, 1965 - November 30, 1965 (Box 11)
  - 47001P - 48000P: August 23, 1965 - October 7, 1965 (Box 12)
  - 48001P - 50000P: June 7, 1965 - September 2, 1965 (Box 13)
  - 51001P - 53000P: December 23, 1964 - March 3, 1965 (Box 14)
  - 53001P - 55000P: March 3. 1965 - May 4, 1965 (Box 15)
  - 55001P - 56000P: May 4, 1965 - June 4, 1965 (Box 16)
  - 47001S - 49000S February 10, 1966 - April 4, 1966 (Box 17)
  - 49001S - 51000S April 4, 1966 - May 27, 1966 (Box 18)
  - 51001S - 53000S May 27, 1966 - August 15, 1966 (Box 19)
  - 53001S - 55000S August 12, 1966 - October 19, 1966 (Box 20)
  - 55001S - 57000S October 19, 1966 - December 12, 1966 (Box 21)
  - 57001S - 57500S December 12 - Dec 20, 1966 (Box 22)
  - 45001S - 47000S December 20, 1966 - February 9, 1967 (Box 23)
  - 44001S - 45000S February 10, 1967 - March 2, 1967 (Box 24)
  - 40001T - 42000T: March 2, 1967 - April 14, 1967 (Box 25)
  - 42001T - 44000T: April 14, 1967 - June 1, 1967 (Box 26)
  - 44001T - 46000T: June 1, 1967 - August 8, 1967 (Box 27)
  - 46001T - 48000T: August 24, 1967 - October 18, 1967 (Box 28)
  - 48001T - 50000T: October 18, 1967 - November 27, 1967 (Box 29)
  - 50001T - 52000T: November 28, 1967 - Jan 17, 1968 (Box 30)
  - 52001T - 54000T: January 17, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 31)
  - 54001T - 54500T: March 20 - March 29, 1968 (Box 32)
  - 14001T - 16000T: March 29, 1968 - June 3, 1968 (Box 33)
  - 16001T - 18000T: June 3, 1968 - July 22, 1968 (Box 34)
  - 18001T - 20000T: July 22, 1968 - October 9, 1968 (Box 35)
  - 20001T - 22000T: Oct 9, 1968 - Jan 28,1969 (Box 36)
  - 22001T - 24000T: December 26, 1968 - March 3, 1969 (Box 37)
  - 24001T - 26000T: March 3, 1969 - May 5, 1969 (Box 38)
  - 26001T - 28000T: May 2, 1969 - July 1, 1969 (Box 39)
  - 28001T - 30000T: July 2, 1969 - September 10, 1969 (Box 40)
  - 30001T - 32000T: September 10, 1969 - November 24, 1969 (Box 41)
  - 32001T - 34000T: November 18, 1969 - February 10, 1970 (Box 42)
  - 34001T - 36000T: February 12, 1970 - May 1, 1970 (Box 43)
  - 36001T - 38000T: May 1, 1970 - July 20, 1970 (Box 44)
  - 38001T - 40000T: July 20, 1970 - September 23, 1970 (Box 45)
  - 15001F - 17000F: September 24, 1970 - December 15, 1970 (Box 46)
  - 17001F - 19000F: December 15, 1970 - March 4, 1971 (Box 47)
  - 19001F - 21000F: March 3, 1971 - July 12, 1971 (Box 48)
- Series VIII: Slavic Acquisitions II
  - 2RI-2R659: October 8, 1962 - December 26, 1962 (Box 1)
  - 3RI-3R700: January 10, 1963 - May 13, 1963 (Box 2)
  - 3R701-3R1344 May 13, 1963 - October 9, 1963 (Box 3)
  - 3R1345-3R1888 October 9, 1963 - December 27, 1963 (Box 4)
  - 4RI-4R750: January 3, 1964 - June 12, 1964 (Box 5)
  - 4R751 - 4R1501 June 6, 1964 - September 23, 1964 (Box 6)
  - 4R1502 - 4R2252 September 23, 1964 - December 23, 1964 (Box 7)
- Series IX: Order Book NASA
  - TR. 1 - 516: 8/23/61 - 7/26/62 (Box 1)
  - 58001H - 600000H: September 14, 1962 - October 4, 1963 (Box 2)
  - 58001M - 59500M: October 4, 1963 - February 28, 1965 (Box 3)
  - 58001P - 59900P: March 1, 1965 - May 16, 1968 (Box 4)
- Series X: Order Books, etc., 1941-1989
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 60000-61499 April 9-November 1, 1941 (Box 1)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 60000-60500 [1941] Duplicate orders (Box 2)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 60501-61000 [1941] Duplicate orders (Box 3)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 61001-61499 [1941] Duplicate orders (Box 4)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 61500-62000 November 13, 1941-June 9, 1942 (Box 5)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 62001-62499 June 1942-April 1943 (Box 6)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 62500-62999 April 15, 1943-September 10, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 63001-63400 September 10, 1945-February 27, 1947 (Box 8)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 63401-63999 February 1947-October 1948 (Box 9)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 64000-64499 October 1948-October 1951 (Box 10)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 64500-65000 November 1951-October 12, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 65001-65500 October 26, 1956-March 18, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 65501-66000 March 18, 1960-February 21, 196 2 (Box 13)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 66001-66500 February 21, 1962-April 22, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 66501-67000 April 22, 1963-March 26, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 67001-67500 March 26, 1964-June 9, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 67501-68000 June 30, 1965-July 15, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 68001-68500 July 15, 1966-January 24, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 68501-68815 January 24, 1968-January 31, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 68816-69500 February 19, 1969-May 1, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 69501-69999 May 1, 1 970- May 21, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 70000-71000 October 26, 1951-January 5, 1954 (Box 22)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 71001-71500 January 5, 1954-October 26, 1956 (Box 23)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]:71501-71700 October 26, 1956-May 24, 1957 (Box 24)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]-71701-72200 May 24, 1957-July 13 (Box 25)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]-72201-72500 July 13, 1959-January 21, 1961 (Box 26)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 72501-73000 January 20, 1961-October 18, 196 2 (Box 27)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 7300173500 October 18, 1962-May 30, 1963 (Box 28)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 73501-74000 March 12, 1963-December 12, 196 3 (Box 29)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 74501-75000 February 20, 1964-November 18 (Box 30)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 75001-75500 November 18, 1966-June 13, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 76001-76800 May 27, 1969-June 25, 1971 (Box 32)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 76801-77300 June 25, 1971-March 27, 1973 (Box 33)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 77301-77788 March 27, 1973-May 13, 1974 (Box 34)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 77789-78300 June 7, 1974-May (Box 35)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 78301-78600 May 29, 1975-June 16, 1976 (Box 36)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 78601-79000 June 16, 1976-June 1, 1977 (Box 37)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 79001-79400 June 21, 1977-May 22, 1978 (Box 38)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 79401-79800 May 22, 1978-November 16, 1979 (Box 39)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 79801-79999 70000A-70200A: November 16, 1979-April 16, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 70201A-70700A: April 16, 1981-June 10, 1983 (Box 41)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 70701A-71300A: June 10, 1983-December 11, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 80001-80500 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 43)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 81001-81500 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 45)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 80501-82000 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 46)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 82001-82500 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 47)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 82501-83000 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 48)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 83001-83500 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 49)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 83501-84000 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 50)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 84001-85000 [ca. 1930s] Duplicate orders (Box 51)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 80000-85000 [ca. 1930s-1940] Duplicate orders (Box 52)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 84501-85000 [no date] (Box 53)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 85001-85999 December 13-May 27, 1940 (Box 54)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 86000-86999 May 27-December 4, 1943 (Box 55)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 87000-87500 December 4, 1945-October 30, 1946 (Box 56)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 87501-88000 November 7, 1946-August 4, 1947 (Box 57)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 88001-88500 August 4, 1947-February 10, 1948 (Box 58)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 88501-89100 February 10-October 28, 1948 (Box 59)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 89101-89700 November 1, 1948-May 26, 1950 (Box 60)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 89701-89999 May 26, 1950-April 11, 1951 (Box 61)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 90000-90500 April 11, 1951-April 18, 1952 (Box 62)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 90501-91000 May 2, 1952-August 14, 1953 (Box 63)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 91001-91500 August 14, 1953-August 23, 1954 (Box 64)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 91501-92000 August 23, 1954-August 22, 1955 (Box 65)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 92001-92500 August 22, 1955-June 15, 1956 (Box 66)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 93001-93325 April 12, 1957-January 24, 1958 (Box 67)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 92501-93000 June 28, 1956-April 12, 1957 (Box 68)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 93326-93500 January 24-June 2, 1948 (Box 69)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 93501-94000 June 2, 1958-June 16, 1959 (Box 70)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 94001-94500 June 16, 1959-May 20, 1960 (Box 71)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 94501-95000 May 20, 1960-April 7, 1961 (Box 72)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 95001-95500 April 7, 1961-February 21, 1962 (Box 73)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 95501-96000 February 21, 1962-November 16, 1962 (Box 74)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 96001-96500 November 15, 1962-July 24, 1963 (Box 75)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 96501-97000 July 24, 1963-February 19, 1964 (Box 76)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 97001-97500 February 19, 1964-August 27, 196 4 (Box 77)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 97501-98000 August 26, 1964-April 26, 1965 (Box 78)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 98001-98500 April 26, 1965-0ctober 22, 1965 (Box 79)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 98501-99000 October 22, 1965-April 11, 1966 (Box 80)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 99001-99500 April l1, 1966-September 29, 196 6 (Box 81)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: 99501-99999 September 29, 1966 April 26, 1967 (Box 82)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: A6000-A6500 May 21, 1971-March 24, 1972 (Box 83)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: A6501-A 6999 March 24, 1972-September 21, 1973 (Box 84)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: A8000-A9000 April 26, 1967-June 30, 1967 (Box 85)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: A8501-A9000 June 30, 1967-July 15, 1968 (Box 86)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: A9001-A9500 July 15, 1968-January 30, 1969 (Box 87)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: A9501-A9999 January 30, 1969-July 28, 1969 (Box 88)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: B6000-B6499 October 10, 1973-January 13, 1975 (Box 89)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: B6500-B6999 January 13, I975- May 7, 1976 (Box 90)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: B8000-B8500 July 28, 1969-January 14, 1970 (Box 91)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: B8501-B9000 January 14, 1970-Apri1 14, 1970 (Box 92)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: B9001-B9500 April 14, 1970-August 20, 1970 (Box 93)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: B9501-B9999 August 20, 1970-January 29, 197 1 (Box 94)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: C6000-C6499 May 7, 1976-February 6, 1978 (Box 95)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: C6500-C6999 February 6, 1978-August 23, 197 9 (Box 96)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: C8000-C8500 January 29, 1971-July 9, 1971 (Box 97)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: C8501-C9000 July 9, 1971-November 24, 1971 (Box 98)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: C9001-C9500 November 24, 1971 August 18, 1972 (Box 99)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: C9501-C9999 August 18, 1972-February 9, 1973 (Box 100)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: D6000-D6499 August 23, 1979-February 24, 198 2 (Box 101)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: D6500-D6999 February 24, 1982-June 15, 1984 (Box 102)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: D8000-D8500 February 16, 1973-November 21, 1973 (Box 103)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: D8501-D9000 November 21, 1973-August 9, 1974 (Box 104)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: D9001-D9500 August 9, 1975-April 4, 197 5 (Box 105)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: D9501-D9999 April 4, 1975-October 27, 1975 (Box 106)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: E6000-E6499 June 15, 1984-May 2, 1986 (Box 107)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: E6500-E6999 May 5, 1985-April 8, 1988 (Box 108)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: E8000-E8500 October 27, 1975-April 16, 1976 (Box 109)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: E8501-E9000 April 16, 1976-December 8, 1976 (Box 110)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: E9001-E9523 December 8, 1976-August 2, 1977 (Box 111)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: E9524-E9999 August 3, 1977-April 18, 1978 (Box 112)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: F8000-F8499 April 18, 1978-March 5, 1979 (Box 113)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: F8500-F8999 March 5, 1979-December 21, 1979 (Box 114)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: F9000-F9500 December 21, 1979-September 24, 1980 (Box 115)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: F9501-F9999 September 24, 1980-March 27, 1981 (Box 116)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: G8000-G8499 March 28, 1981-April 2, 1982 (Box 117)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: G8500-G8999 April 2, 1982-January 15, 1983 (Box 118)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: G9000-G9499 January 15, 1983-September 12, 1983 (Box 119)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: G9500-G9999 September 12, 1983-May 8, 1984 (Box 120)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: H8000-H8499 May 8, 1984-December 31, 1984 (Box 121)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: H8500-H8999 December 31, 1984-August 2, 1985 (Box 122)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: H9000-H9499 August 2, 1985-May 7, 1986 (Box 123)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: H9500-H9999 May 7, 1986-June 30, 1987 (Box 124)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: J8000-J8499 June 30, 1987-July 5, 1988 (Box 125)
  - Order Book [Standing Orders]: J8500-J8999 July 5, 1988-May 31, 1989 (Box 126)
  - Green Book "Periodicals" J9000-J9499 (Box 127)
  - Slavic Continuation Orders: 74001-74298 (Box 128)
  - Spiral Notebook: "70000s Orders" May 25, 1983 (Box 129)
  - Spiral Notebook: "70000s Orders" October 6, 1988 (Box 130)
  - Blue Book "Continuations F6000-F6499" (Box 131)
  - Blue Book, no label (beginning slip No. 71573A July 5, 1985 last slip No. 71279A February 11, 1985) (Box 132)
  - Large blue book "70000 titles" (list of books and dates ordered) (Box 133)